<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Software engineering for integrated systems on SEIS-Blog</title><link>https://nilslenaerts.github.io/seis-nilslenaerts/</link><description>Recent content in Software engineering for integrated systems on SEIS-Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 15:13:10 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nilslenaerts.github.io/seis-nilslenaerts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The WebAssembly compiler: WAT?</title><link>https://nilslenaerts.github.io/seis-nilslenaerts/post/compiler/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 15:13:10 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nilslenaerts.github.io/seis-nilslenaerts/post/compiler/</guid><description>To be able to run WebAssebly we first have to compile the WebAssembly text file to a WebAssembly binary. To be able to do this we will be writing our own basic compiler from scratch which will translate WebAssembly WAT files to WASM files.
this will be done in three distinct steps
Lexing Parsing Compiling The Lexer: nearly all programming languages are made up of different words and symbols to make a complex program but how does a compiler know what is a class identifier or a string or a comment that is the job of the lexer.</description></item><item><title>Chapter VI: Esmeralda</title><link>https://nilslenaerts.github.io/seis-nilslenaerts/post/chapter-6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://nilslenaerts.github.io/seis-nilslenaerts/post/chapter-6/</guid><description>We are delighted to be able to inform the reader, that during the whole of this scene, Gringoire and his piece had stood firm. His actors, spurred on by him, had not ceased to spout his comedy, and he had not ceased to listen to it. He had made up his mind about the tumult, and was determined to proceed to the end, not giving up the hope of a return of attention on the part of the public.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://nilslenaerts.github.io/seis-nilslenaerts/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nilslenaerts.github.io/seis-nilslenaerts/about/</guid><description>Illustration from Victor Hugo et son temps (1881) The Hunchback of Notre-Dame (French: Notre-Dame de Paris) is a French Romantic/Gothic novel by Victor Hugo, published in 1831. The original French title refers to Notre Dame Cathedral, on which the story is centered. English translator Frederic Shoberl named the novel The Hunchback of Notre Dame in 1833 because at the time, Gothic novels were more popular than Romance novels in England.</description></item></channel></rss>